Everything is under control.
If I Had Legs I'd Kick You is a drama film directed by Mary Bronstein.
With her life crashing down around her, Linda attempts to navigate her child's mysterious illness, her
absent husband, a missing person, and an increasingly hostile relationship with her therapist.
Linda, played by Rose Byrne.
Therapist, played by Conan O'Brien.
James, played by A$AP Rocky.
Caroline, played by Danielle Macdonald.
Child, played by Delaney Quinn.
Dr. Spring, played by Mary Bronstein.
If I Had Legs I'd Kick You is a 2025 American psychological
comedy-drama film, written and directed by Mary Bronstein.
It stars Rose Byrne, Conan O'Brien, Danielle Macdonald,
Delaney Quinn, Christian Slater, and A$AP Rocky.
The film had its world premiere at the Sundance Film Festival on January 24, 2025, and a domestic release by A24 on October 10, 2025, to positive reviews, with Byrne's performance receiving universal
acclaim, earning her the Silver Bear for Best Leading Performance and a Golden Globe Award, alongside nominations for the Critics' Choice Award, Actor Award and Academy Award for Best Actress.
The film explores themes of hotel, therapist, female
protagonist, sick child, motherhood.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.